Hi my name is Brian Estrada
and Im the director of Hair Jitsu.
The inspiration for Hair Jitsu comes from
my best friends daughter Adrianna.
And she has this hair thats down past her knees.
The conversation came up about whats going to happen
when you guys finally cut her hair?
Growing up I took Taekwondo for...
about 7 years and it was a huge part of my life back then.
Watching Kung Fu movies also was huge
Like the Bruce Lee movies with my dad.
So when I started here I was a production assistant and...
It was awesome that sepergee came up, kinda shows that
Ideas come up from anywhere in the studio
and Im really grateful that I got the opportunity to do that
To showcase my talent to be a filmmaker